Guide to the Josef Silverstein papers, [ca. 1950-1990]
Silverstein, Josef papers, [ca. 1950-1990]
- Series II. Newspaper Clippings
  - Material, Original Documents, and Josef Silverstein Notes on David Marshall as Chief Ministry of Singapore (3 of 3), 1954-1956 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Burma Newspaper Clippings, 1956-1958 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Burma, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Josef Silverstein Notes of Federalism, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Dupoy Article on Burma Army, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Josef Silverstein Notes for Essay, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Josef Silverstein Notes, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Clippings, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Burma, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Burma Army, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Burma for Pol., 1961 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Burma Karen, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Burma Kayah State, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Clippings (1 of 3), 1961 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Clippings (2 of 3), 1961 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Clippings (3 of 3), 1961 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Burma Parliament, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Burma Election, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Burma Student, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Burma Civil Rights, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Regionalism Issues, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Burma, 1961-1962 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Revolutionary Council Federalism State Affair, 1962, March (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Revolutionary Council Party Activities, March 2, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Clippings (1 of 2), 1962 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Clippings (2 of 2), 1962 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Shan State Politics, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Josef Silverstein Interview Notes with Education Minister, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Josef Silverstein Notes on 1922 Books (Young Burma), 1962 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Arakan, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - National Character, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Burma Revolutionary Council Orders and Activities, 1962, March (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - 4 Year Plan z91961) and Other Aspects of Planning, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Revolutionary Council Statements in Press Comments Editorials, 1962, March (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - March Revolutionary Council Economic Activity, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Pyidaunsu Party, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Burma Parliament, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Burma Mon State-Mon Politics, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Burma, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Workers, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Korean War, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Karen, Shans, and KMT, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - KMT in Laos, August 10, 1961 - 1962, October (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Burma Chronicle: Originals, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - ML WJ Government, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Chin State (Chin Division Politics), 1962 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Burma, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Internal Burmese Repercussion Politics, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Taiwan Press, KMT Burma and Indonesia, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - The Foreign Policy of the Union of Burma-Wm. Marshall Wright, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Burma, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Rule for Formation of Council Peoples’ Work, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Land Nationalization Rules-Original in Burmese, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Josef Silverstein Manuscript and Buddhism as State Religion and Publication Notes (1 of 2), 1964, mid 1960s (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Josef Silverstein Manuscript and Buddhism as State Religion and Publication Notes (2 of 2), 1964, mid 1960s (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Burma, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Burma (1 of 2), 1966 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Burma (2 of 2), 1966 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Burma, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Malaysia for Pol., 1968 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Malaysia for Devaluation and Root, 1967-1968 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Malaysian Students, 1967-1968 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Education Policy (Malaysia), 1968 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Malaysia-Thailand Affair, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Singapore Elections, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Malaysia Politics, Parties, and Question of Unity (1 of 2), 1968 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Malaysia Politics, Parties, and Question of Unity (2 of 2), 1968 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Frankovic, Kathy, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - CK Burma Lecture U.S. and Asia, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Burma Press Clippings, 1968-1972 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Background of Burma, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Burma, 1968-1969 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Burma, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Law New Win Period (Burma), 1969 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Burma Newspaper Clippings, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Burma, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Constitution Material, Burma-Ne Win Period, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Josef Silverstein Notes, Burma Research Project, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Burma Foreign Affairs, Ne Win Period, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Army, Burma-Ne Win Period, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Politics and Admins (1 of 2), 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Politics and Admins (2 of 2), 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - First Draft of Constitution, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Burma, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Burma Research Congress (Abstract of Papers), 1973 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Papers, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Burma (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Burma (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Burma, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Burma, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - KMT Burma, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Council of Foreign Relation, Burma, July 29, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Burma Newsletter, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Burma, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Burma (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Burma (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Burma (1 of 2), 1982 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Burma (2 of 2), 1982 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Burma, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Silverstein Articles, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Burma, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Silverstein Articles, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Burma (1 of 3), 1985 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Burma (2 of 3), 1985 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Burma (3 of 3), 1985 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Silverstein Articles, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Burma (1 of 2), 1986 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Burma (2 of 2), 1986 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Silverstein Articles, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Burma (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Burma (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Forwards Magazine and Clippings, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Silverstein Articles, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Burma (1 of 2), 1988, Jan.—July (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Burma (2 of 2), 1988, Jan.—July (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1988, July1 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1988, August (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Clippings (1 of 2), 1988, Sept.—Nov. (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Clippings (2 of 2), 1988, Sept.—Nov. (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1988, Oct.—Nov. (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1988, Oct. (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1988, Dec. (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Silverstein Articles, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Burma, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Clippings (1 of 2), 1989, Jan.—June (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Clippings (2 of 2), 1989, Jan.—June (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Clippings (1 of 2), 1989, May—June (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Clippings (2 of 2), 1989, May—June (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Clippings, 1989, July (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Clippings, 1989, Aug. (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Burma, 1989, Sept. (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Clippings, 1989, Oct. (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Clippings, 1989, Nov.—Dec. (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - The Manifesto of the National League for Democracy, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Silverstein Articles, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Clippings (1 of 2), 1990, April-June (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Clippings (2 of 2), 1990, April-June (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Clippings (1 of 3), 1990, Mar.-Dec. (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Clippings (2 of 3), 1990, Mar.-Dec. (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Clippings (3 of 3), 1990, Mar.-Dec. (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1990, Jan.-Mar. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - PRO: Burma, 1990-1992 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Silverstein Articles, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - News Clippings (1 of 2), 1991, Jan.-June (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - News Clippings (2 of 2), 1991, Jan.-June (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, 1991, July-Aug. (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, 1991, Sep.-Dec. (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Clippings, Various (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Clippings, Various (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Silverstein Articles, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Clippings (1 of 2), 1992, Jan.-Dec. (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Clippings (2 of 2), 1992, Jan.-Dec. (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Burma, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Silverstein Articles, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Burma (1 of 4), 1993 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Burma (2 of 4), 1993 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Burma (3 of 4), 1993 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Burma (4 of 4), 1993 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Silverstein Articles, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Burma (1 of 2), 1994 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Burma (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - News (1 of 2), 1994 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - News (2 of 2), 1994 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - News, 1994, July (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - News, 1994, Aug.-Dec. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Silverstein Articles, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - News Clippings, Burma Presse, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - News (1 of 3), 1995, Jan. (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - News (2 of 3), 1995, Jan. (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - News (3 of 3), 1995, Jan. (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - News (1 of 3), 1995, June (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - News (2 of 3), 1995, June (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - News (3 of 3), 1995, June (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - News, 1995, Aug.-Dec. (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Burma, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - News (1 of 2), 1996, Jan. (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - News (2 of 2), 1996, Jan. (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - News (1 of 2), 1996, June (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - News (2 of 2), 1996, June (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - News (1 of 3), 1996, July-Aug. (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - News (2 of 3), 1996, July-Aug. (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - News (3 of 3), 1996, July-Aug. (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - News (1 of 2), 1996, Sept. (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - News (2 of 2), 1996, Sept. (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - News (1 of 2), 1996, Oct. (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - News (2 of 2), 1996, Oct. (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - News (1 of 2), 1996, Nov. (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - News (2 of 2), 1996, Nov. (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - News (1 of 3), 1996, Dec. (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - News (2 of 3), 1996, Dec. (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - News (3 of 3), 1996, Dec. (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - News, 1997, Jan. (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - News (1 of 2), 1997, Feb. (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - News (2 of 2), 1997, Feb. (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - News (1 of 3), 1997, Mar. (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - News (2 of 3), 1997, Mar. (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - News (3 of 3), 1997, Mar. (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - News (1 of 3), 1997, Apr. (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - News (2 of 3), 1997, Apr. (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - News (3 of 3), 1997, Apr. (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - News (1 of 2), 1997, May (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - News (2 of 2), 1997, May (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - News (1 of 2), 1997, Jun. (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - News (2 of 2), 1997, Jun. (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - News (1 of 3), 1997, Jul. (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - News (2 of 3), 1997, Jul. (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - News (3 of 3), 1997, Jul. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - News, 1997, Aug. (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - News, 1997, Sep. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - News (1 of 3), 1997, Oct. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - News (2 of 3), 1997, Oct. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - News (3 of 3), 1997, Oct. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - News (1 of 2), 1997, Nov. (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - News (2 of 2), 1997, Nov. (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - News (1 of 2), 1997, Dec. (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - News (2 of 2), 1997, Dec. (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - News (1 of 2), 1998, Jan. (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - News (2 of 2), 1998, Jan. (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - News, 1998, May-Jun. (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - News (1 of 2), 1998, Jul. (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - News (2 of 2), 1998, Jul. (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - News (1 of 2), 1998, Aug. (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - News (2 of 2), 1998, Aug. (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - News (1 of 3), 1998, Sept. (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - News (2 of 3), 1998, Sept. (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - News (3 of 3), 1998, Sept. (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - News (1 of 2), 1998, Oct. (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - News (2 of 2), 1998, Oct. (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - News (1 of 2), 1998, Nov. (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - News (2 of 2), 1998, Nov. (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - News (1 of 2), 1998, Dec. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - News (2 of 2), 1998, Dec. (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - News (1 of 2), 1999, Jan. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - News (2 of 2), 1999, Jan. (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - News (1 of 2), 1999, Feb. (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - News (2 of 2), 1999, Feb. (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - News (1 of 2), 1999, Mar. (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - News (2 of 2), 1999, Mar. (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - News (1 of 2), 1999, Apr. (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - News (2 of 2), 1999, Apr. (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - News (1 of 2), 1999, May (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - News (2 of 2), 1999, May (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - News (1 of 2), 1999, Jun. (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - News (2 of 2), 1999, Jun. (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - News (1 of 2), 1999, Jul. (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - News (2 of 2), 1999, Jul. (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - News (1 of 3), 1999, Aug. (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - News (2 of 3), 1999, Aug. (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - News (3 of 3), 1999, Aug. (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - News (1 of 2), 1999, Sept. (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - News (2 of 2), 1999, Sept. (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - News (1 of 3), 1999, Nov. (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - News (2 of 3), 1999, Nov. (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - News (3 of 3), 1999, Nov. (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - News (1 of 3), 1999, Dec. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - News (2 of 3), 1999, Dec. (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - News (3 of 3), 1999, Dec. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - News (1 of 3), 2000, Jan. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - News (2 of 3), 2000, Jan. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - News (3 of 3), 2000, Jan. (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - News (1 of 3), 2000, Feb. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - News (2 of 3), 2000, Feb. (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - News (3 of 3), 2000, Feb. (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - News (1 of 3), 2000, Mar. (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - News (2 of 3), 2000, Mar. (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - News (3 of 3), 2000, Mar. (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - News (1 of 4), 2000, Apr. (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - News (2 of 4), 2000, Apr. (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - News (3 of 4), 2000, Apr. (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - News (4 of 4), 2000, Apr. (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - News (1 of 4), 2000, May (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - News (2 of 4), 2000, May (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - News (3 of 4), 2000, May (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - News (4 of 4), 2000, May (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - News (1 of 4), 2000, June (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - News (2 of 4), 2000, June (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - News (3 of 4), 2000, June (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - News (4 of 4), 2000, June (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - News (1 of 4), 2000, Jul. (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - News (2 of 4), 2000, Jul. (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - News (3 of 4), 2000, Jul. (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - News (4 of 4), 2000, Jul. (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - News (1 of 4), 2000, Aug. (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - News (2 of 4), 2000, Aug. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - News (3 of 4), 2000, Aug. (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - News (4 of 4), 2000, Aug. (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - News (1 of 4), 2000, Sep. (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - News (2 of 4), 2000, Sep. (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - News (3 of 4), 2000, Sep. (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - News (4 of 4), 2000, Sep. (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - News (1 of 4), 2000, Oct. (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - News (2 of 4), 2000, Oct. (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - News (3 of 4), 2000, Oct. (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - News (4 of 4), 2000, Oct. (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - News (1 of 3), 2000, Nov. (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - News (2 of 3), 2000, Nov. (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - News (3 of 3), 2000, Nov. (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - News (1 of 4), 2000, Dec. (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - News (2 of 4), 2000, Dec. (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - News (3 of 4), 2000, Dec. (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - News (4 of 4), 2000, Dec. (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Burma (1 of 3), 2001, Jan. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Burma (2 of 3), 2001, Jan. (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Burma (2 of 3), 2001, Jan. (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - News (1 of 4), 2001, Feb. (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - News (2 of 4), 2001, Feb. (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - News (3 of 4), 2001, Feb. (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - News (4 of 4), 2001, Feb. (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - News (1 of 4), 2001, Mar. (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - News (2 of 4), 2001, Mar. (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - News (3 of 4), 2001, Mar. (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - News (4 of 4), 2001, Mar. (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - News (1 of 4), 20 01, Apr. (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - News (2 of 4), 20 01, Apr. (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - News (3 of 4), 20 01, Apr. (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - News (4 of 4), 20 01, Apr. (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - News (1 of 4), 2001, May. (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - News (2 of 4), 2001, May. (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - News (3 of 4), 2001, May. (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - News (4 of 4), 2001, May. (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - News (1 of 4), 2001, Jun. (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - News (2 of 4), 2001, Jun. (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - News (3 of 4), 2001, Jun. (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - News (4 of 4), 2001, Jun. (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Burma (1 of 3), 2001, Jul. (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Burma (2 of 3), 2001, Jul. (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Burma (3 of 3), 2001, Jul. (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - News (1 of 2), 2001, Aug. (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - News (2 of 2), 2001, Aug. (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Burma (1 of 3), 2001, Sep. (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Burma (2 of 3), 2001, Sep. (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Burma (3 of 3), 2001, Sep. (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Burma Net (1 of 3), 2001, Oct. (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Burma Net (2 of 3), 2001, Oct. (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Burma Net (3 of 3), 2001, Oct. (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Burma Net (1 of 2), 2001, Nov. (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Burma Net (2 of 2), 2001, Nov. (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - News (1 of 2), 2001, Dec. (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - News (2 of 2), 2001, Dec. (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - News (1 of 3), 2002, Jan. (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - News (2 of 3), 2002, Jan. (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - News (3 of 3), 2002, Jan. (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - News, 2002, Feb. (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - News (1 of 3), 2002, Mar. (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - News (2 of 3), 2002, Mar. (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - News (3 of 3), 2002, Mar. (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - News, 2002, Apr. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - News (1 of 2), 2002, May (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - News (2 of 2), 2002, May (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - News, 2002, Jun. (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - News (1 of 2), 2002, Jul.-Aug. (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - News (2 of 2), 2002, Jul.-Aug. (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - News (1 of 2), 2002, Sep. (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - News (2 of 2), 2002, Sep. (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - News (1 of 2), 2002, Oct. (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - News (2 of 2), 2002, Oct. (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - News, 2002, Nov. (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - News (1 of 2), 2002, Dec. (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - News (2 of 2), 2002, Dec. (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - News, 2003, Jan. (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - News (1 of 2), 2003, Feb. (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - News (2 of 2), 2003, Feb. (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - News (1 of 2), 2003, Mar. (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - News (2 of 2), 2003, Mar. (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - News, 2003, Apr. (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - News, 2003, May (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - News (1 of 3), 2003, Jun. (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - News (2 of 3), 2003, Jun. (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - News (3 of 3), 2003, Jun. (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - News, 2003, Jul. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - News (1 of 2), 2003, Aug. (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - News (2 of 2), 2003, Aug. (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - News (1 of 2), 2003, Sep. (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - News (2 of 2), 2003, Sep. (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - News (1 of 3), 2003, Oct. (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - News (2 of 3), 2003, Oct. (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - News (3 of 3), 2003, Oct. (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - News, 2003, Nov. (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - News (1 of 3), 2003, Dec. (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - News (2 of 3), 2003, Dec. (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - News (3 of 3), 2003, Dec. (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - News (1 of 3), 2004, Jan. (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - News (2 of 3), 2004, Jan. (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - News (3 of 3), 2004, Jan. (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - News, 2004, Feb. (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - News (1 of 3), 2004, Mar. (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - News (2 of 3), 2004, Mar. (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - News (3 of 3), 2004, Mar. (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - News (1 of 3), 2004, Apr. (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - News (2 of 3), 2004, Apr. (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - News (3 of 3), 2004, Apr. (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - News (1 of 3), 2004, May (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - News (2 of 3), 2004, May (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - News (3 of 3), 2004, May (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - News, 2004, Jun. (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - News, 2004, Jul. (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - News (1 of 3), 2004, Aug. (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - News (2 of 3), 2004, Aug. (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - News (3 of 3), 2004, Aug. (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - News, 2004, Sep. (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - News (1 of 2), 2004, Oct. (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - News (2 of 2), 2004, Oct. (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - News (1 of 2), 2004, Nov. (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - News (2 of 2), 2004, Nov. (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - News (1 of 2), 2004, Dec. (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - News (1 of 2), 2004, Dec. (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Burma: Charting the way to Freedom, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - SPDC National Convention: The Detailed Basic Principles, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Human Rights, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Committee on the Rights of the Child, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - National Democratic Front, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - The Constitutional Committee on the Revelation of the People’s Aspiriations, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Human Rights Special Rapporteur, 2004, 2005, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - News (1 of 2), 2005, Jan (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - News (2 of 2), 2005, Jan (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - News, 2005, Feb. (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - News (1 of 3), 2005, Mar. (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - News (2 of 3), 2005, Mar. (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - News (3 of 3), 2005, Mar. (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - News, 2005, Apr. (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - News (1 of 2), 2005, May (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - News (2 of 2), 2005, May (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - News (1 of 2), 2005, Jun. (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - News (2 of 2), 2005, Jun. (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - News (1 of 2), 2005, Jul. (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - News (2 of 2), 2005, Jul. (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - News, 2005, Aug. (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - News, 2005, Sep. (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - News (1 of 2), 2005, Oct. (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - News (2 of 2), 2005, Oct. (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - News, 2005, Nov. (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - News, 2005, Dec. (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Constitution (1 of 3), 2005 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Constitution (2 of 3), 2005 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Constitution (3 of 3), 2005 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Constitution-Odd Bits, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - UN-SPDC-NLD-Others Worldwide, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Taylor/Independent Report, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - News, 2006, Jan. (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - News, 2006, Feb. (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - News, 2006, Mar. (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - News (1 of 4), 2006, Apr. (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - News (2 of 4), 2006, Apr. (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - News (3 of 4), 2006, Apr. (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - News (4 of 4), 2006, Apr. (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - News (1 of 3), 2006, May (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - News (2 of 3), 2006, May (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - News (3 of 3), 2006, May (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - News, 2006, Jun. (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - News, 2006, Jul. (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - News, 2006, Aug. (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - NCGUB: National Coalition Government of the Union of Burma, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Clippings, 2007 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - News, 2007, Jan. (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - News, 2007, Feb. (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - News, 2007, Mar. (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - News, 2007, Apr. (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - News, 2007, May (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - News, 2007, Jun. (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - News, 2007, Jul. (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - News, 2007, Aug. (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - News, 2007, Sep. (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - News, 2007, Nov. (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - News, 2007, Dec. (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Josef Silverstein Correspondence, 2007-2008 (Box 43, Folder 3)